Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead."
《行尸走肉》前情提要
That true?
是真的吗
You wanna help?
你想帮忙
- I do. - Okay.
-是的  -好
We have to get ready. We have to fight.
我们要做好准备  我们必须反抗
We do.
是的
we get you the guns, we fight together.
我们给你找到枪  然后一起战斗
- Say yes. - Yes.
-说同意  -同意
They're out there, so I'm gonna be there with you.
他们在外面  所以我要跟你去
We are.
我们要去
Package deal.
买一送一
You have to get me something.
你必须给我搞些东西来
A knife, a gun...
刀  枪
This will do it. It's a poison.
用这个就行  这是毒药
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
官方合作
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
□|
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
创意 周边
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
我爱美剧
52meiju.taobao.com
淘
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
原创翻译  双语字幕
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
最新连载海外影视剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com 仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Hey, darlin'.
亲爱的
Wake up.
醒醒
Hey, darlin'. Wake up.
亲爱的  醒醒
What is it? Do we need to --
怎么了  我们需要...
No, no, no. We're okay for now.
不用  暂时没事
Well, good afternoon to you.
你也下午好
You're here.
你来了
Yeah.
是啊
And I'm feelin' all kinds of glad to see you right now.
现在见到你  我浑身舒服
Are they back?
他们回来了吗
Not yet.
还没
I know you were pullin' late shift, and you wanna tonight,
我知道你最近上夜班  今晚也是
so I didn't want to wake you up.
所以我不想吵醒你
Maggie's in trouble.
玛姬有麻烦了
What?
什么
Something with the baby.
孩子出了问题
Rick's taking her to the doctor at Hilltop.
瑞克要带她去找山顶寨的医生
He doesn't know it yet, but I'm going with him.
他还不知道  但我要跟他去
I just...
我只是
I know we just started this,
我知道我们才刚开始
- but I wanted you to -- Don't.
-但我希望你...  -别
"Don't" what?
别什么
Don't go.
别走
Welcome to the first day of the rest of your life, Sasha.
欢迎来到你余生的第一天  萨沙
You are gonna help make sure things get back on track today.
你今天要帮我确保一切回到正轨
You are smart, hot as hell, dignified as shit,
你聪明性感  尊严高尚
and you don't suffer one goddamn fool.
眼里容不得蠢货
No one's gonna wanna watch you die.
没人想看你死
I don't wanna see that.
我就不想
So you don't have to.
所以你没必要死
But someone does.
但总得有人死
Maybe a couple others -- tops.
最多几个人
But not you and not most people.
但你不用死  大部分人也不用死
We are gonna help solve some shit.
我们要解决一些问题
Tuck in.
尽情吃吧
Big day.
今天是个大日子
What do you need from me?
你需要我做什么
Look at me.
看着我
Why?
为什么
'Cause I want it stopped.
因为我想阻止这一切
I want Negan dead.
我要尼根死
So why don't you kill him?
那你为什么不杀他
Can't just be me.
我一个人做不到
They're all Negan.
他们都是尼根
That girl you murdered...
你谋杀的那个女孩
She had a name.
她有名字
Her name was Denise, and she was a doctor.
她叫丹妮斯  是一名医生
And she helped people.
她救助了很多人
I wasn't aiming for her.
我瞄的不是她
Do it. Do it.
动手  动手
You wanna end it this way...
你想这样结束
You go ahead.
随便你
I'm sorry. I am.
我很抱歉  真的
I know you want to.
我知道你很想
He could just be here to see if you were here.
他可能只是来打探你是否在这里的
We can't trust him.
我们不能信任他
He owned me.
我曾是他的人
But not anymore.
但不再是了
What I did,
我过去做的事
I was doing it for someone else.
都是为了某个人
She just got away.
她最近跑掉了
So now I'm here.
所以我来了
So are you because of her?
那你是为了她吗
Do it!
动手啊
There's another choice.
你还有另一个选择
Daryl.
达里尔
- Daryl, you knew her. - Negan trusts me.
-达里尔  你认识她  -尼根信任我
We can work together, we can stop him.
我们可以合作  我们可以阻止他
You knew me then, and you know me now.
你认识之前的我  也认识现在的我
You know I'm not lying.
你知道我没有撒谎
I'm not.
我没有
Do it.
动手啊
Do it!
动手
They have Sasha, if she's even alive.
他们抓住了萨沙  如果她还活着的话
Why didn't you say something?
你为什么不早说
He could be our only chance to get her back.
他可能是我们救回她的唯一机会
Because I don't trust him.
因为我不信任他
But I trust Daryl.
但我信任达里尔
Negan's coming soon.
尼根马上就要来了
Tomorrow.
明天
Three trucks probably.
大概会来三辆卡车
20 saviors and him.
他和二十名救世军
I can slow them down,
我可以拖住他们
bring some trees down in the road,
弄些树把路挡住
buy a little time for you guys to get ready.
为你们争取一点准备的时间
If you can take them out, that's where we start.
假如你们能把他们干掉  我们就起了个好头
You kill them, I'll radio back to the sanctuary.
你们杀了他们之后  我会发消息到救世堂
The sanctuary?
救世堂
Where negan lives.
尼根的住处
That's what they call it.
他们是这么叫的
I can radio back to them and say everything's okay.
我会发消息给他们  告诉他们一切顺利
You drive the trucks back,
你们把卡车开回去
and I can lead you right inside,
我可以领着你们直捣黄龙
and, with the right plan, we can wipe out the rest.
假如计划得好  我们能把残党都干掉
Check to see if your friend's still alive.
再去看看你们的朋友是否还活着
Then, we get the workers on our side,
然后我们把工人拉拢到我们这边
build our numbers up,
增加人数
and go from outpost to outpost and end this.
然后一个个哨站杀过去  结束这一切
Keep talking.
继续说
We just started it -- the whole thing.
我们刚挑起了大战
If he's lyin', I'm gonna kill him real slow.
假如他在撒谎  我会慢慢折磨死他
When this is done,
等这一切结束了
I don't give a damn if he's sorry.
我才不管他是不是悔过了
I will kill that son of a bitch.
我会杀了那个混蛋的
If he's lying,
假如他在撒谎
this is already over.
我们早已完了
Oh, I gotta go.
我得走了
Fact is, I figured we'd --
事实上  我觉得我们可以...
I had a dream.
我做了一个梦
You...
你...
You had a dream about me?
你梦到我了吗
You died.
你死了
That's the plan.
计划就是这样
That's what I need from you.
这就是我需要你做的事
And when you come out, not a peep.
你出来的时候  别吱声
They will stand down, if they haven't already.
他们会投降  假如他们还没投降的话
And then, Lucille here, well, she gets her three,
然后  露西尔会杀掉三个人
and we move forward with a new understanding.
然后我们带着全新的认知继续前行
Are you -- are you shitting me?
你是在...你是在逗我吗
Is that real?
那是真的眼泪吗
I can do it, but no one has to die.
我可以配合  但没必要杀人
You are wrong.
你错了
Punishment --
惩罚...
Can't do anything without that.
没它什么都做不成
Punishment is how we built everything we have.
我们拥有的一切都是建立在惩罚之上的
You think I'm gonna sit here and let you...
你以为我会坐视你...
Careful!
当心点
You are not letting me do anything.
我做什么轮不到你管
No one has to die.
没必要死人
Okay.
好吧
How about this?
这样如何
One.
一个
Just one.
只死一个
I mean, I was gonna pull three outta the pool,
我本来打算选三个
but just one,
但只杀一个
and just for you.
专门为了你
Okay.
好
Just one person has to die.
只用死一个人
You got me wrapped around your little finger.
你真是把我玩弄于股掌之间
You know that?
知道吗
And it's not a man woman thing.
这跟男女无关
I mean, if you had a dick,
我是说  就算你有根老二
I would still have these feelings.
我还是会有这种感觉的
We roll out in 45.
45分钟后出发
So we don't have Oceanside, but we have their guns.
我们没争取到海边旅馆  但我们有她们的枪
Negan has Sasha.
而尼根手里有萨沙
Daryl wants us to trust Dwight.
达里尔希望我们相信德怀特
Rick wants us to stay here in case things go wrong
瑞克希望我们留在这以防不测
so there's another card to play,
这样还有另一手牌可打
another safe place the Saviors think they control.
另一个救世军以为受他们控制的安全之处
But he doesn't know that Gregory's gone...
但他不知道格雷戈里已经离开了
That maybe he's telling them things,
也许他告诉了他们一些事
that'll make them think something else.
会让他们改变想法
And it's all about to happen.
这些都是会发生的
You're thinking of leading the Hilltop over there to fight.
你在考虑领导山顶寨反抗
I am.
是的
If Negan finds out they're planning something,
如果尼根发现他们在计划什么
they're gonna need help,
他们就需要帮助了
Even with those scavengers on their side.
虽然那些拾荒者都站在他们那边
Well, you'd have to decide right now,
你必须现在就决定
and it's a very tough decision.
这是个艰难的决定
Why are you smiling?
你笑什么
'cause I'm glad you're the one making it for us.
因为我很高兴你是为我们做决定的人
How do I?
该怎么决定
I don't know.
我不知道
I just know you can.
我只知道你能做出决定
Let me take her.
我来照顾她
You take this.
你拿着这个
Guns up, now.
端起枪
What the hell? He's dead.
怎么回事  他已经死了
What is it?
怎么了
We've seen this before.
以前见过这个
Same ones.
跟以前一样
Dude, you okay?
伙计  你没事吧
- You're gonna ambush them on your own? - Yeah.
-你要一个人伏击他们吗  -对
Going alone doesn't work for this.
现在不可以一个人单干
It works for me.
我可以
Have you killed any of them?
你杀过他们的人了吗
Because if you have and they've found out,
因为如果你杀过  并且被他们发现了
they may think it was the Kingdom,
他们也许会认为是神之国干的
and we lose our advantage.
我们会失去有利条件
It's from walkers.
这是行尸的血
Can we move them aside?
我们能把路障移开吗
Do you seek to extinguish everything of who you were?
你欲抹杀从前的自己吗
I don't seek it, but...
没有  但是
I'm stuck.
我不知所从
You want the Saviors dead?
你想让救世军们死吗
- Morgan. - Yes, I do.
-摩根  -是的
Cease this folly.
停止你的愚行
Accompany my regiment.
加入我的军队
The Saviors are a dragon with many heads,
救世军好似多头巨龙
their numbers legion.
兵多将广
We must seek allies in this endeavor.
我们必须联合盟友与之一战
That's Benjamin's armor.
那是本杰明的盔甲
Do you wear it to serve you, or do you wear it in his honor?
你穿着是为了保护自己  还是为了纪念他
Morgan...
摩根
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
最新海外影视剧下载
You are not stuck.
你没有走投无路
Join us on this journey to create an alliance.
加入我们的旅程  结为盟友
Fight with us,
和我们一起战斗
and we shall defeat them so that no one will suffer
我们会打败他们  不会再让别人
under their capricious malevolence ever again.
被他们玩弄蹂躏
And we start once more for the fallen...
我们为了逝者
for the Kingdom...
为了神之国
...for the glory of victory.
为了胜利的荣耀再次战斗
What you fight for.
你们为何而战
Not the place -- the people, each other.
不是为了这个地方  而是为了彼此
You're a part of that now.
现在你们也是我们的一员了
We take. We don't bother --our way.
我们只拿  不费心  这是我们的方式
Maybe another way.
也许该换种方式了
Yours?
你男人吗
Yeah, we're together.
我们是在一起
I lay with him after.
我过后要睡他
You care?
你介意吗
- We should get back to work. - Yeah.
-该回去干活了  -是啊
Think this was them?
你觉得是他们干的吗
Crossed my mind.
我想过
We got a plan "B."
我们有后备计划
If I might be so bold...
恕我直言
this unexpected stoppage has given me
这突然的阻碍让我
the chance for an exhaustive mull.
有机会能好好考虑一下
Now, given the loaded circumstances
根据现在的严峻形势
and potential for casualties and resource expenditure,
还有潜在伤亡和资源消耗
I was wondering if you would give me the opportunity
你能不能给我个机会
to attempt to slow their jets and cool their roll.
去劝降他们  让他们冷静
You shoot one of these before?
你以前用过这种枪吗
Good.
很好
Worry?
担心吗
No.
不
Good.
很好
- I'll be on the next one over. - Why?
-我去另一个塔  -为什么
It's more sight lines if we split up.
分头行动视野更好
I'll go.
我去
You sure?
你确定吗
Okay.
好吧
We win.
我们会赢
Yeah.
是啊
You know what's gonna happen,
你知道会发生什么事
How this is gonna end.
这会如何结束
We're gonna walk out that door together.
我们要一起走出那扇门
We kick shit and eat snakes.
同甘共苦
- That's us. - We can sit this one out.
-我们就是这样  -我们这次可以不管
They need us here, anyway.
反正他们也需要我们留在这
Rick said to get ready for a fight.
瑞克说要准备好战斗
How'd I die?
我怎么死的
We were at the beach.
我们当时在沙滩上
It was before.
是在灾变前
You got pulled under...
你被水卷了进去
And you didn't come back up.
没能出来
I was trying to find you, but you were gone.
我试着去找你  但是你不见了
And then, I started to drown.
然后  我开始溺水
I hate the beach.
我讨厌沙滩
End of the day in a wet suit?
穿着橡胶衣玩一天
It's like you're sandblasting your nutsack
回到车上的每一步
every single step you take back to the car.
蛋都像在被喷砂
Luckily, the seaside ain't on the agenda today.
还好今天不去海边
Just security and some road to chew.
只是守卫和赶路
All right? So, come on.
好吗  来吧
- Let's go help Maggie. - Abraham.
-我们去帮玛姬  -亚伯拉罕
What?
什么
They can use us here.
这里需要我们
Just once, we sit one out.
就这一次  我们不逞英雄
- Someone else -- - it should be us.
-别人...  -应该是我们
Maggie's gotta take care of maggie.
玛姬应该靠自己
Have you, uh, changed your mind
吃过敏药的事
about taking that allergy medication?
你有没有改变主意
- Yes. - Good.
-有  -很好
I think you'll get adjusted to the place, sinus-wise.
我觉得你会适应这个地方的
No, I won't.
不会的
Not like you.
不像你
Everyone has a way out.
每个人都有自己的出路
Don't go and yuck my yum for takin' mine,
别因为我的选择批判我
which, I may add, is the same as yours now.
顺便说  你也选的一样
If people die today, it's 'cause of the choices they made.
如果今天有人死  都是自己选的
Yeah. It is.
是啊  确实如此
Why are we here?
我们在这里做什么
For this.
等这个
Rosita.
罗西塔
Get into position.
就位
I'll signal you.
我给你信号
And the wall's gonna hold?
墙没问题吧
It'll hold.
没问题
All points are covered.
你们已被包围
Every contingency is already met.
所有意外都在考虑内
I come armed with two barrels of the truth.
我带着真相前来
A test is upon you, and I'm giving out the cheat sheet.
大考将至  而我给你们带来了小抄
H-hello.
你们好
I come salved with the hope that it is my dropped knowledge that you heed.
我前来劝降  因为我知道你们通情达理
Options are zero to none.
你们没有选择余地
Compliance and fealty are your only escape.
忠诚服从是唯一出路
Bottom-lining it -- you may thrive, or you may die.
说白了  你们可生  亦或死
I sincerely wish for the former
我衷心希望是前者
For everyone's sake.
为了所有人着想
The jig is up and in full effect.
你们已经完全暴露了
Will you comply, rick?
你们投降吗  瑞克
Where's Negan?
尼根在哪
I'm Negan.
我是尼根
No.
不
We win.
我们会赢
You ever hear the one about the stupid little prick named rick
你听过叫瑞克的小傻瓜
who thought he knew shit but didn't know shit
以为自己本事大却一无所知
and got everyone he that gave a shit about killed?
害自己在乎的人被杀光的故事吗
It's about you.
说的就是你
You're all gonna wanna put your guns down now.
你们最好都把枪放下
No one drops anything.
所有人都别放下枪
We had a deal.
我们说好的
Tamiel came for the boat things.
塔米尔去拿船上物资
Followed ones who took.
跟踪了夺走物资的人
Made a better deal.
做了笔更好的交易
You push me, and you push me. And you push me, Rick.
你一而再  再而三地逼我  瑞克
You just tried to blow us up, right?
你刚才想炸了我们是吧
I mean, I get me, my people.
你想弄死我和我的人  我懂
But Eugene?
但是尤金呢
He's one of yours.
他可是你的人
And after what he did -- he stepped up.
他做了那事之后  洗心革面了
You people...
你们这些人
are animals.
真是禽兽
Universe gives you a sign, and you just
上帝给了你们启示
shove your finger right up its ass.
你们却回了个中指  捅了他的菊花
Dwight, Simon, chop-chop.
德怀特  西蒙  快去
So, you don't like Eugene anymore.
好吧  你们不喜欢尤金了
You guys gotta like Sasha.
但你们肯定喜欢萨沙
I do, too.
我也喜欢她
Got her right here packaged for your convenience,
为了方便你们  我把她装在这里面了
alive and well.
毫发无损
Now, I brought her so I wouldn't have to kill all of you,
我带来了她  就不用杀了你们所有人了
and not killing all of you could get complicated.
但不把你们都杀了  事情会变得很复杂
See, I know there's a lot of firepower left in there, Rick.
我知道里面还有很多武器  瑞克
So I'm gonna make this simple.
我的要求很简单
I want all the guns you've managed to scrape up.
我要你们想方设法积攒来的所有枪
Yep, I know about those, too.
是的  这个我也知道
I want every last grain of lemonade you got left.
我要你们剩下的所有柠檬粉
I want a person of your own choosing...
我还要你选一个人
For Lucille.
送给露西尔
Daryl --
达里尔
Ooh, I gotta get me my Daryl back.
我得要回我的达里尔
I see you.
我看到你了
And the pool table
还有台球桌
and all the pool cues and chalk.
全部台球杆和巧粉
And I want it now
我现在就要
or Sasha dies,
不然萨沙就得死
And then all of you.
然后你们所有人都得死
Probably.
大概吧
C'mon, Rick.
行了  瑞克
Just because I brought her in a casket
我把她装在棺材里带来
doesn't mean she has to leave in it.
不意味着她就得死在里面
You know what?
你知道吗
You suck ass, Rick.
你逊毙了  瑞克
You really do.
真的
I don't want to have to kill her,
我不想杀她
but that's exactly what you're gonna make me do.
但这正是你逼我要做的事情
Let me see her.
让我看看她
All right. Just give me a second.
好吧  给我点时间
I might have to get her up to speed.
我也许得跟她说说现在什么情况了
You can't hear shit inside this thing.
在棺材里可什么都听不到
Sash.
萨沙
You're not gonna believe this crap.
你绝对不会相信这破事的
It felt real.
感觉很真实
Like we lost this.
像是失去了这一切
And this just started.
而我们才刚刚开始
- C'mon. - Wait.
-走吧  -等等
I like the way you call bullshit.
我喜欢你看穿我的样子
So let me return the favor.
所以这次让我来帮帮你吧
The next thing you're gonna tell me
接下来你要跟我说的是
is that you'll go and that I can stay.
你会去  这样我就可以留下
Because I know you didn't like hearing yourself just say
因为我知道  你自己也不想说出
that, "Maggie's gotta take care of Maggie."
"玛姬应该靠自己"这种话
I know those words are gonna choke in your ears
我知道这句话会萦绕在你脑中
a good, long while
很久很久
and you're gonna wanna make up for even thinking that.
你会因为仅仅有这念头而做出补偿
Am I right?
我说得对吗
Yeah.
对
We lay our big meaties across the chopping block ahead of someone else's.
我们为别人置生死于度外
It's always for someone else.
总是为别人
Both of us know, if we're gonna kick,
我们都知道  如果我们要死
there sure as hell better be a point to it.
那最好死得有意义
So maybe we feel there was a-a point to all of this.
所以或许我们觉得这一切都是有意义的
Alpha to omega.
自始至终
Whether it's on the battlefield or the beach
不管是在战场  还是在海边
or somewhere out there today.
还是别的什么地方
Maggie --
玛姬
She's carrying the future.
她怀着未来
You're right.
你说得对
I knew how this was gonna end.
我就知道会这样
C'mon.
走吧
Layin' your ass on the line for someone else,
为别人冒生命危险
Tearin' it to shreds for 'em --
为他们扫除障碍
You said it before.
你以前说过
Oh, my, that is living.
这才叫活着
You're an idiot.
你真是个傻瓜
I never said otherwise.
我从没说过我不是
A couple hours to get there, right?
去那里要几个小时  对吗
At least.
至少吧
Might be a circuitous and janky route.
路上也许障碍重重
With what they're planning, they could be watching the roads.
鉴于他们在谋反  道路很可能被监视了
"What they're planning."
"他们在谋反"
That's right.
没错
Got it in the marketplace. It's chock-full.
我在市集拿的  存满了歌
Doubt conversation will be on tap for the commute.
在途中恐怕无法交谈
And though I am a selfish coward,
尽管我是个自私的懦夫
I do tend to think of other people on occasion.
我有时也会为别人着想
Please take it with my compliments.
请收下我的馈赠吧
I truly wish I measured up.
我真心希望我能做好人
You still can, Eugene.
你依然可以  尤金
I'm not giving up.
我不会放弃
Not on you.
不会放弃你
Jesus, you don't have to take the trip in the thing.
天啊  你不用躺在那玩意儿里面过去
I could use the rest.
我想休息一下
No shit?
不是吧
Yeah.
是的
I just want to go to sleep.
我只想睡觉
I just need a little bottle of water, and I'm fine.
给我一小瓶水就行了
Arat?
阿拉特
Listen...
听着
I know how tough this is.
我知道这有多难
And I appreciate it.
我很感激
Damn, you are something else.
该死  你真了不得
Sash.
萨沙
You're not gonna believe this crap.
你绝对不会相信这破事的
Holy goddamn!
我的妈呀
Go! Go!
快走
No.
别
Aah! honey, god damn it!
亲爱的  该死
Plan "B" It is!
那就后备计划吧
Down. Now.
跪下  快点
We can make another deal.
我们可以重新做笔交易
I said, down.
我说了跪下
Hello again.
又见面了
Down. Or again.
跪下  不然再吃一枪
Well, shit, Rick.
靠  瑞克
You just couldn't stick with us, huh?
你就不能老实跟着我们吗
You had to go with these filthy garbage people?
非要找这些捡破烂的脏人
No offense.
无意冒犯
Deal is for 12, yes?
说好了是12个  对吗
10.
10个
People are a resource.
人才是资源
12.
12个
10.
10个
Rick.
瑞克
This is just gonna make you sad.
这会让你难过的
Broken.
心碎
You're gonna wish you were dead.
你会希望你死了
I like having fun.
我喜欢闹着玩
I do.
真的
But maybe you think that the guy that did what he did to your friends wasn't me,
但也许你觉得对你朋友做出那种事的人不是我了
like that was some sort of a put-on,
以为那不过是某种作秀
like I'm not the guy with the bat --
以为我不是拿着大棒的人
I'm just the guy that makes your kid spaghetti.
只是个给你孩子做意面的人
Oh, shit.
靠
Maybe this is on me.
也许这怪我
Maybe this is all on me.
也许这全都怪我
I gotta make it right.
我必须纠正错误
I guess I gotta start all over again.
我猜又要重来一遍了
I gotta tell you, Rick,
必须告诉你  瑞克
if I had a kid,
假如我有孩子
I'd want him to be just like your kid,
我希望他跟你孩子一样
which makes this so much harder.
所以这就更难了
You're not gonna win.
你赢不了的
Carl.
卡尔
It is over.
已经结束了
Why don't you point your one ball
何不用你的独眼
up the street there and take it all in?
看看那边  感受一下
We'll win!
我们会赢
We live!
我们会活
We're the ones!
是我们
Us!
我们
You just lost somebody important to you right now -- like, just now.
你刚失去了某个重要的人  就在刚刚
Jesus.
老天啊
That is timing.
时机刚好
Well, Rick...
瑞克
you chose this.
这是你选的
I truly don't know what more I could've done to warn you.
我真不知道我还能怎么警告你
And this isn't a warning.
而且这不是警告了
This is punishment.
这是惩罚
I'm gonna kill Carl now.
我现在要杀了卡尔
I'm gonna make it one nice, hard swing,
我会狠狠地  重重地挥一棒
try to do it in one because I like him.
试着一击毙命  因为我喜欢他
I just want you to put that in your brain
我只想让你把这个念头放进脑子里
and roll it around for a minute.
细细回味一下
I'm gonna kill Carl, and then Lucille here,
我会杀了卡尔  然后露西尔
she's gonna take your hands.
她会砸烂你的双手
You can do it right in front of me.
你可以就在我面前做
You can take my hands.
你可以砸烂我的双手
I told you already --
我已经告诉过你了
I'm gonna kill you.
我会杀了你
All of you.
你们所有人
Maybe not today, maybe not tomorrow...
也许不在今天  也许不在明天
but nothing is gonna change that --
但没有什么能改变这点
Nothing.
没有什么
You're all already dead.
你们已经死了
Damn.
靠
Wow, Rick.
瑞克
Okay.
好吧
You said I could do it.
你说了我可以做
End these Saviors and their accomplices!
灭了救世军和他们的同伙
Alexandria will not fall, not on this day!
亚历山大不会陷落  不在今天
Phalanx out, third group, now!
方形阵  第三队  上
Move up! Now we got your backs!
上  我们掩护你们
A goddamn tiger!
他妈的一头老虎啊
That widow is alive, guns a-blazin'!
那寡妇没死  活蹦乱跳的
You taste that, Simon? That is the taste of shit!
你尝到了吗  西蒙  这就是吃屎的滋味
They're falling back.
他们撤退了
Eduardo, Bertie, between the houses --
爱德华多  伯蒂  去房屋之间
Cover the gate!
掩护大门
Let's go.
走
Now we finish this!
现在收尾
Now!
上
Pull! ?
拉
Michonne.
米琼恩
Oh, you're alive.
你还活着
We -- W-We're...
我们...
I know. I know. ?
我知道  我知道
I know.
我知道
We are.
我们活下来了
We will.
我们会活下去
Getting preparations in place.
准备已就绪
Everyone's on "Blue level."
所有人都是蓝色警戒
You say the word, they're ready to go.
只要你下令  他们就出发
That's good.
很好
How the hell do you think she wound up dead in that box?
你觉得她怎么会死在棺材里
My, um, best possible posit fingers the tarp.
最可能的原因是油布
That sealed up said box good and tight.
棺材被封得严严实实
She ran out of air.
没氧气了
Maybe.
也许吧
So...
那么
we are going to war!
我们要开战了
Yes, sir!
遵命
Do you think Sasha did that herself?
你觉得萨沙是一个人做到的吗
I don't know how, but I know she did.
我不知道怎么做到的  但我知道她做到了
She gave us a chance. You did.
她给了我们机会  你给了我们机会
You made the right decision to come.
你选择过来是正确的
The decision was made a long time ago,
这选择很早以前就做了
before any of us knew each other,
在我们大家相识之前
when we were all strangers who would have just passed each other on the street
当我们还是在街上擦肩而过的陌生人时
before the world ended.
在世界结束之前
And now we mean everything to each other.
现在我们对彼此意味着一切
You were in trouble. You were trapped.
你遇到了麻烦  你陷入了困境
Glenn didn't know you, but he helped you.
格伦不认识你  但他救了你
He put himself in danger for you.
他为你冒了生命危险
And that started it all --
这是一切的源头
From Atlanta, to my daddy's farm,
从亚特兰大  到我爸爸的农场
to the prison,
到监狱
to here...
到这里
to this moment now...
到此时此刻
not as strangers --
我们不再是陌生人
as family...
而是家人
because Glenn chose to be there for you that day
因为格伦那天选择救了你
a long time ago.
很久很久以前
That was the decision that changed everything.
而那个选择改变了一切
It started with both of you,
这是你们俩发起的
and it just grew...
然后不断壮大
to all of us...
如今我们所有人
to sacrifice for each other...
为彼此做出牺牲
to suffer and stand,
承受苦难
to grieve, to give,
去哀悼  去给予
to love, to live...
去爱  去生活
to fight for each other.
去为彼此而战
Glenn made the decision, Rick.
格伦做出了那个选择  瑞克
I was just following his lead.
我不过是在追随他的脚步